<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sevDesk Tech Blog</title><link>https://tech.sevdesk.com/</link><description>Recent content on sevDesk Tech Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 11:58:42 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tech.sevdesk.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How agile teams work at sevDesk</title><link>https://tech.sevdesk.com/posts/how-agile-teams-work-at-sevdesk/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 11:58:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://tech.sevdesk.com/posts/how-agile-teams-work-at-sevdesk/</guid><description>End to end responsibility A couple of months ago we re-organized most of our agile dev teams.
Our teams now have end-to-end responsibility which makes them much more autonomous. If you look at the frontend of sevDesk you’ll see different parts like “Invoices”, “ERP” and many more. One team now manages exactly one part of our app - from frontend over backend down to the database.
The teams themselves consist of members with different specialities: Product Owner, Agile Coach, Frontend Dev, Backend Dev and also UX/UI.</description></item><item><title>Time to give something back - our blog begins</title><link>https://tech.sevdesk.com/posts/time-to-give-something-back-our-blog-begins/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 11:58:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://tech.sevdesk.com/posts/time-to-give-something-back-our-blog-begins/</guid><description>Hey everyone!
A journey starts sevDesk was founded in 2013. We started with that tiny idea of making accounting simpler for small businesses.
Back then we were not sure about how to make money. In the first years we physically installed sevDesk on servers of our customers. We also tried to sell whitelabled versions of sevDesk. And we tried to sell sevDesk as online application.
In the end the online application (aka SaaS application) really worked for us, and this is what sevDesk is now.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://tech.sevdesk.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tech.sevdesk.com/about/</guid><description>sevDesk is a company that makes accounting for small businesses as enjoyable as a great afternoon at the beach.
We are a tech company and we love what we do.
That&amp;rsquo;s why we are running this blog. To give some insights. Discuss ideas how we work. And maybe inspire people with some lessons we learned in the last years :)
We are growing and are hiring - also remotely. Check out our career pages.</description></item></channel></rss>